<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Cristian Rohr</title>
    <link>https://cristianrohr.xyz/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Cristian Rohr</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 18:24:09 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cristianrohr.xyz/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>History of &#39;Convivencia&#39; a generative art project - and its personal background</title>
      <link>https://cristianrohr.xyz/posts/convivencia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 18:24:09 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cristianrohr.xyz/posts/convivencia/</guid>
      <description>About the project Convivencia is a generative art project in the Tezos network. It consists of 350 pieces and will be available on the fxhash platform.
&amp;lsquo;Convivencia&amp;rsquo; is a Spanish word that means coexistence. The title has a background, which I will explain in the end of the post, first I want to tell the characteristics and challenges encountered during the development.
Test mint for Convivencia
This project has a number of substantial differences with respect to my previous projects, namely:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing CR Art Sessions on fx(hash)</title>
      <link>https://cristianrohr.xyz/posts/art_session/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cristianrohr.xyz/posts/art_session/</guid>
      <description>In Argentina there is a very young and talented music producer called BIZARRAP.
He is very famous for the BZRP Music Sessions, which are tracks in collaboration with international artists that Bizarrap produces in his studio, which also serves as a recording studio for the official video clip of the track.
In these sessions the artists have the freedom to express themselves in ways that perhaps the industry doesn&amp;rsquo;t allow them because they have an image to sell, or the freedom to deliver whatever they want.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
